[{"question":"What can you set a reminder for in Outlook?","options":[{"text":"all of these answers","correct":true},{"text":"contacts","correct":false},{"text":"email messages","correct":false},{"text":"appointments and meetings","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":"What is the default permission that other people in your organization have to your calendar?","options":[{"text":"none of these answers","correct":true},{"text":"They can edit.","correct":false},{"text":"They can view all details.","correct":false},{"text":"They can view titles and locations.","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":"Your boss sends you an email with a request to set up a meeting and copies all meeting attendees on the message. What is the fastest way to create the calendar appointment","options":[{"text":"Click New Items > New Appointment.","correct":false},{"text":"Click Calendar > New Meeting, and then copy and paste information as needed.","correct":false},{"text":"with the email open, click Meeting on the Home ribbon or Message tab.","correct":false},{"text":"Click Reply All.","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":"You are running low on Outlook storage space. How might you address this problem?","options":[{"text":"all of these answers","correct":true},{"text":"Archive messages you are done with.","correct":false},{"text":"Save and then remove large attachments from messages","correct":false},{"text":"Sort by size and then delete large messages.","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":"Why are read receipts less reliable than delivery receipts?","options":[{"text":"A and C","correct":false},{"text":"B and C","correct":false},{"text":"A and B","correct":false},{"text":"A,B,and C","correct":false}],"illustrator":"```\nA. Users can change their email settings to ignore requests for read receipts.\nB. Users can decline individual requests for read receipts.\nC. Read receipts are expensive, so some organizations turn them off.\n```"},{"question":"What address box should you use if you want to hide message recipients from each other?","options":[{"text":"Bcc","correct":true},{"text":"to","correct":false},{"text":"cc","correct":false},{"text":"From","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":"You are creating a new email message to Diane and Joey. You need a response from Diane, but are simply informing Joey. How should you address the email?","options":[{"text":"to Diane and Joey","correct":false},{"text":"to Diane and bcc Joey","correct":false},{"text":"to Joey and bcc Diane","correct":false},{"text":"to Diane and cc Joey","correct":true}],"illustrator":""},{"question":"Which choice is not an attachment?","options":[{"text":"a PDF document included with an email","correct":false},{"text":"a Word document included with an email","correct":false},{"text":"(Ã‚) a calendar item included with an email","correct":false},{"text":"a hyperlink included in an email","correct":true}],"illustrator":""},{"question":"You can use a**\\_to indicate that a message requires further action and a**to organize the message.","options":[{"text":"folder; category","correct":false},{"text":"flag; tag","correct":true},{"text":"category; flag","correct":false},{"text":"flag; category","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":" You create a task and assign it to Nalia. Nalia reviews the request and declines the assignment. Where is the task now, and who is the owner?","options":[{"text":"The task is nowhere, and no one is the owner.","correct":false},{"text":"The task is in your task list, and you are the owner.","correct":false},{"text":"The task is in Nalia's task list, and you are the owner.","correct":false},{"text":"The task is in Nalia's task list, and Nalia is the owner until she reassigns it to you.","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":" What does Outlook automatically point out to you when you are invited to a meeting?","options":[{"text":"if your attendance is mandatory","correct":false},{"text":"ifthe meeting is high or low priority","correct":false},{"text":"the amount of time you have between this meeting and your next event","correct":false},{"text":"if the meeting is adjacent to another event in your calendar","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":" What appears on your screen whenever a new email arrives?","options":[{"text":"an emoji","correct":false},{"text":"an alert","correct":false},{"text":"a notice","correct":false},{"text":"a bell icon","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":" Some of your inbox folder are used for annual or biannual projects, while others are used for work that is not based on projects. The same is true for your calendars. How can you use archiving to increase your efficiency and minimize the size of your mailbox?","options":[{"text":"Review your folders to determine the age of messages that should auto archive in each folder. Set the most frequent value as the AutoArchive default","correct":false},{"text":"For each folder, determine whether aged items should be deleted or archived","correct":false},{"text":"Set individual settings for folders that should be archived, but not using the default settings","correct":false},{"text":"All of these answers","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":" Removing redundant messages can be completed by utilizing what Outlook features?","options":[{"text":"Filter","correct":false},{"text":"Junk Mail","correct":false},{"text":"The Delete Key","correct":false},{"text":"Clean Up Conversation","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":" You have sent several emails to a customer and have not received a response. What option do you set to know whether the customer receives your messages?","options":[{"text":"Delivery receipt","correct":false},{"text":"All of these answers","correct":false},{"text":"Read receipt","correct":false},{"text":"Tracking","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":" A message on your summary list appears with a paper clip icon and an arrow pointing to the left. What does this indicate?","options":[{"text":"The message has been replied to and contains an attachment","correct":false},{"text":"The message has been flagged and contains an attachment","correct":false},{"text":"None of these answers","correct":false},{"text":"The message has been forwarded and contains an attachment","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":" What is a key difference between sending someone your Outlook contact and sending you Outlook business card?","options":[{"text":"Sending the contact is faster because the contact itself has no formatting","correct":false},{"text":"Sharing a contact is superior because more email systems support Outlook contacts rather than business cards","correct":false},{"text":"There is no real difference","correct":false},{"text":"Your business card can be edited to omit personal information such as a home phone","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":" You have received an email message with detailed notes that you need to analyze before responding, so you want to save it as a task. What is the best way to create a new task that includes the notes in the body of the task?","options":[{"text":"Right click the email message, drag and drop it on the Tasks icon, and click Copy Here as Task with Attachment","correct":false},{"text":"Copy and paste the notes into a new task form","correct":false},{"text":"Drag the email message and drop it on the Tasks icon","correct":false},{"text":"Right click the email message, drag and drop it on the Tasks icon, and click Move Here as Task with Attachment","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":" There are two types of Outlook rules. One is server-based rules, which run for Exchange Server. What are the other kind, which in part or in whole cannot run on Exchange Server, and when do the execute?","options":[{"text":"client-only rules; when Outlook is running","correct":false},{"text":"Outlook-based rules; when Outlook is running","correct":false},{"text":"None of these answers","correct":false},{"text":"Outlook-only rules; when Outlook is offline","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":" In earlier version of Outlook, you could easily apply a color to messages sent only to you, but the messages on which you were cc'd were still a visual distraction. How might you create an Inbox experience that is more focused than the default Outlook experience?","options":[{"text":"Create a CCd folder, and then create a rule to move all messages where you are on the CC line to that folder","correct":false},{"text":"Create a rule to move all messages where you are in the CC line to the Deleted Items folder","correct":false},{"text":"Create a rule to apply conditional formatting to all messages where you are in the CC line","correct":false},{"text":"Turn on Focused Inbox","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":" How can you quickly locate emails with large attachment?","options":[{"text":"Sort the messages by size then filter by Has: Attachments","correct":false},{"text":"Sort the messages by sender","correct":false},{"text":"Sort the messages by Has: Attachments and then filter by Is: Large","correct":false},{"text":"Sort the messages by Has: Attachments and then by size","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":" What is not a built-in search filter for message folder?","options":[{"text":"Has Attachments","correct":false},{"text":"Sent to me as Bcc","correct":false},{"text":"Categorized","correct":false},{"text":"Not sent directly to me","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":" You created a meeting for next Friday at 1 PM, and several invitees have accepted. How do you change only your version of the meeting to 12 PM to allow time to setup?","options":[{"text":"Double click the meeting to open its form, and then change the start time and close it","correct":false},{"text":"None of these answers","correct":false},{"text":"Open the calendar in Day, Week, or Work Week view and drag the start time to 12 PM","correct":false},{"text":"You must create a separate appointment for yourself from 12 PM to 1 PM","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":" What is the fastest way to find a message sent by Bonnie Bradford that includes an attachment?","options":[{"text":"Search based on sender then filter by Has Attachments","correct":false},{"text":"Search for \"has:attachments\" and then filter by Bonnie Bradford","correct":false},{"text":"All of these answers","correct":false},{"text":"Enter \"Bonnie Bradford attachment\" in the search box","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":" Each category must have a unique \\_\\_\\_","options":[{"text":"color","correct":false},{"text":"folder","correct":false},{"text":"name","correct":false},{"text":"name and color","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":" Outlook autocompletes email addresses you have used previously, including addresses that you mistyped. How can you remove an incorrect autocomplete suggestion?","options":[{"text":"Search the autocomplete library, select the incorrect suggestion, and then click Delete","correct":false},{"text":"Close Outlook, reboot your computer, and restart Outlook","correct":false},{"text":"Wait until the suggestion appears again, then highlight it and press the Delete key","correct":false},{"text":"Delete the corresponding contact","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":" What is the key difference between an appointment and a meeting?","options":[{"text":"A meeting includes other people","correct":true},{"text":"An appointment is automatically marked as busy while a meeting is marked as tentative","correct":false},{"text":"An appointment can be all day, while a meeting has specific start and end time","correct":false},{"text":"A meeting has specific start and end times","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":" When adding an email account to Outlook, why might you need to enter the server settings manually?","options":[{"text":"You did not write down your password","correct":false},{"text":"Outlook cannot detect the proper settings for your server automatically","correct":true},{"text":"You do not have an email server","correct":false},{"text":"The server is not on the list of Microsoft approved servers","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":" You are viewing a date three months in the future, in Month view. You switch to check an email in the same window. When you switch back to the calendar, what will Outlook display?","options":[{"text":"the current month","correct":false},{"text":"the Month view for a date three months in the future","correct":false},{"text":"the current date in Day view","correct":false},{"text":"the current date in Week view","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":" When you @mention a colleague in an email message, what does not happen?","options":[{"text":"Your colleague's name is highlighted in the message","correct":false},{"text":"The colleague is automatically added to the To line","correct":false},{"text":"@ appears next to the message in your colleague's Inbox","correct":false},{"text":"@ appears next to the email in your Sent items folder (Sent folder in Outlook for Mac)","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":" You have received an email messages with detailed notes that you need to analyze before responding, so you want to save it as a task. What is the best way to create a new task that includes the notes in the body of the task?","options":[{"text":"Right-drag the email message, drop it on the Tasks icon, and click Copy Here as Task with Attachment","correct":false},{"text":"Drag the email message and drop it on the Tasks icon","correct":false},{"text":"Copy and paste the notes into a new task form","correct":false},{"text":"Right-drag the email message, drop it on the Tasks icon, and click Move Here as Task with Attachment","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":" What is an appropriate use for voting buttons?","options":[{"text":"Asking your supervisor to prioritize a list of tasks","correct":false},{"text":"Sending customers a three-question survey about a recent service experience","correct":false},{"text":"Asking your colleagues to choose their favorite lunch spot from a list","correct":false},{"text":"All of these answers","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":" You created a meeting for next Tuesday at 2 PM, and several invitees have accepted. How do you change the meeting so it will begin at 1 PM and last for one hour?","options":[{"text":"B","correct":false},{"text":"C","correct":false},{"text":"A or B","correct":true},{"text":"A","correct":false}],"illustrator":"```\nA. Open the calendar in Day, Week, or Work Week view. Drag the start time to 1 PM and send an update\nB. Double click the meeting to open it, change the start time to 1 PM abd send an update\nC. Some people have already accepted, so you must cancel this meeting and create a new meeting\n```"},{"question":" What permission allows your delegates to read, create, change, and delete items that they create, but not items that you created?","options":[{"text":"Reader","correct":false},{"text":"Author","correct":false},{"text":"Reviewer","correct":false},{"text":"Editor","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":" Why might you create an additional contacts folder?","options":[{"text":"To store contacts to share with colleagues","correct":false},{"text":"To avoid exceeding 500 contacts per folder limit","correct":false},{"text":"To make it faster to search for your contacts","correct":false},{"text":"All of these answers","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":" What is a key difference between flagging a message for follow up and creating a task from them?","options":[{"text":"All of these answers","correct":false},{"text":"A task can be assigned to another person while a flagged item cannot be delegated","correct":false},{"text":"You can set a reminder for a task but not for a flagged item","correct":false},{"text":"The flagged message appears only in the Inbox folder; the task appears in the To-Do Bar and task list","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":" When accepting a meeting invitation, what happens if you click \"Do not send a response\"?","options":[{"text":"Outlook will send an email to the meeting organizer on your behalf","correct":false},{"text":"The meeting organizer will not receive an email with your response, and your response will be recorded","correct":false},{"text":"The meeting organizer will not receive an email with your response, and your response will not be recorded","correct":false},{"text":"None of these answers","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":" What happens to your calendar when you adjust the time scale?","options":[{"text":"You set time constraints for looking events","correct":false},{"text":"You automatically switch to list view","correct":false},{"text":"You change the time zone that your calendar uses","correct":false},{"text":"You change the number of hours visible on the grid","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":" Which is not a good reason to create a new calendar?","options":[{"text":"To keep track of personal events in a work setting","correct":false},{"text":"To use a shared calendar with colleagues","correct":false},{"text":"To isolate meetings and important dates for a project team","correct":false},{"text":"To have a different view of your calendar","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":" Under what conditions can you successfully recall a message?","options":[{"text":"Only when the recipient is also using Outlook","correct":false},{"text":"Only if the email is plain text without attachments","correct":false},{"text":"If the email si still in your outbox","correct":false},{"text":"If the email was sent within the past 24 hours","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":" What rule can you create in View Settings to color code messages from a particular senderm such as your manager?","options":[{"text":"Format Columns","correct":false},{"text":"Conditional Formatting","correct":false},{"text":"Group By","correct":true},{"text":"By Sender","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":" You have a contact folder for members and you need to track two additional pieces of member information: start date and last renewal. What is the simplest wat to track this information?","options":[{"text":"Export your contacts to Excel, which ash lots of columns; add the data; and then import the contacts back to Outlook","correct":false},{"text":"Use the Field Chooser to create two new columns of type Date in the folder","correct":false},{"text":"Create a custom contacts form that includes two text boxes to collect this data","correct":false},{"text":"All of these answers","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":" You have created a rule to automatically route emails to the Project A folder. Why might you also add Project A to Favorites? (Select all that apply)","options":[{"text":"A and C","correct":false},{"text":"A, C, and D","correct":false},{"text":"A and B","correct":false},{"text":"B and D","correct":false}],"illustrator":"```\nA. To easily see when you have a new message related to Project A\nB. To audit the rule\nC. Because the unread messages count for the Inbox folder will not include Project A\nD. Because you cannot create a search folder for a subfolder\n```"}]